[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "What does FBLA stand for?",
        "options": [
            "Future Blooming Leaders of America",
            "Future Business Leaders of America",
            "Future Bundle Leaders of America",
            "Future Business Leaders of Austria"
        ],
        "answer": "Future Business Leaders of America"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: FBLA holds regional competitions",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "FBLA stands for: Future ________ Leaders of America",
        "answer": "business"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are true about FBLA-PBL? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a college program",
            "It is a high school program",
            "It has an entry fee of $150"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a high school program",
            "It is a college program"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "What is the full form of the BAA?",
        "answer": "business achievement awards"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the events to their type",
        "options": [
            "A) Solo test",
            "B) Individual",
            "C) Teams of up to three"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Cyber Security",
            "Introduction to Social Media Strategy",
            "Impromptu Speaking",
            "Introduction to Business",
            "Digital Video Production"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Cyber Security": "A",
            "Introduction to Social Media Strategy": "C",
            "Impromptu Speaking": "B",
            "Introduction to Business": "A",
            "Digital Video Production": "C"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "What state is FBLA-PBL headquartered in?",
        "options": [
            "Virginia",
            "Washington",
            "Maryland",
            "California"
        ],
        "answer": "Virginia"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: FBLA was founded over 100 years ago",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "First name of the founder of FBLA-PBL (in the 1900s)",
        "answer": "hamden"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are divisions of FBLA-PBL? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "FBLA",
            "FBLA-ML",
            "FBLA-Professional Division",
            "FBLA-College Program"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "FBLA",
            "FBLA-ML"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "Current president and CEO of FBLA-PBL (first and last name)",
        "answer": "Alexander Graham"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the events to their category",
        "options": [
            "A) Presentation",
            "B) Report",
            "C) Speech"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Business Ethics",
            "Business Plan",
            "Public Speaking",
            "Client Service",
            "Impromptu Speaking"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Business Ethics": "A",
            "Business Plan": "B",
            "Public Speaking": "C",
            "Client Service": "A",
            "Impromptu Speaking": "C"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "How many people are enrolled in FBLA?",
        "options": [
            "More than 200,000",
            "More than 150,000",
            "More than 80,000",
            "More than 50,000"
        ],
        "answer": "More than 200,000"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: The FBLA is one of the top 10 organizations listed by the US Dept of Education",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "The full form of PBL is: Phi ____ Lambda",
        "answer": "Beta"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "FBLA is present in which countries? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "India",
            "Canada",
            "Hungary",
            "Kazakhstan"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Canada",
            "Hungary",
            "Kazakhstan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "What is the full name of FBLA's college division?",
        "answer": "Phi Beta Lambda"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the descriptions to their BAA level",
        "options": [
            "A) Future",
            "B) Leader",
            "C) Business"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Business skills and introduction to community service",
            "emphasis on regional FBLA involement and community leadership",
            "advanced business skills",
            "national FBLA involvement, and focus on becoming community leaders",
            "emphasizes the importance of getting involved with FBLA locally"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Business skills and introduction to community service": "A",
            "emphasis on regional FBLA involement and community leadership": "C",
            "advanced business skills": "B",
            "national FBLA involvement, and focus on becoming community leaders": "B",
            "emphasizes the importance of getting involved with FBLA locally": "A"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "How many people can participate in the Computer Game and Simulation Programming event as a group?",
        "options": [
            "Up to 4",
            "Up to 3",
            "Up to 2",
            "Only 1"
        ],
        "answer": "Up to 3"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: There are 5 levels of the BAA",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "Level one of the BAA is: ______",
        "answer": "Future"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which BAA events have their deadline on March 1? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "Serivice",
            "Leader",
            "Business",
            "America"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Leader",
            "Business"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "What is the core concept of the BAA which focuses on improving a member's school?",
        "answer": "service"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the required activity to the associated BAA award",
        "options": [
            "A) Future",
            "B) Business",
            "C) America"
        ],
        "words": [
            "5 hours of community service",
            "Video promoting a competitive event",
            "Flyer promoting FBLA",
            "75 hours of community service",
            "Get a letter of recommendation about your leadership skills"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "5 hours of community service": "A",
            "Video promoting a competitive event": "B",
            "Flyer promoting FBLA": "A",
            "75 hours of community service": "C",
            "Get a letter of recommendation about your leadership skills": "C"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "What attire must be worn to FBLA events?",
        "options": [
            "Formal",
            "Business Casual",
            "Casual",
            "Flip-Flops"
        ],
        "answer": "Business Casual"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: 'Knowledge' is one of the core concepts of the BAA",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "The _____ ______ Chapter Challenge has chapters complete 10 tasks revolving around recruitment",
        "answer": "super sweeps"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are additional FBLA programs? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "National Awards program",
            "Adviser Wall of Fame",
            "Forkner award",
            "Sweep Stakes challenge"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "National Awards program",
            "Adviser Wall of Fame"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "At which event are national officers elected?",
        "answer": "national leadership conference"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the American Enterprise Day activites to the level at which they would be organized",
        "options": [
            "A) Elementary Schools",
            "B) Middle/High School",
            "C) College/Uniersity"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Organize a panel of experts to discuss the pros and cons of owning a business",
            "Assign essays on the American enterprise system",
            "Present songs and skits about American enterprise",
            "Design a workbook about filling out job applications and the different occupations possible",
            "Sponsor a 5 month forum on American enterprise, spanning multiple topics"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Organize a panel of experts to discuss the pros and cons of owning a business": "C",
            "Assign essays on the American enterprise system": "B",
            "Present songs and skits about American enterprise": "A",
            "Design a workbook about filling out job applications and the different occupations possible": "B",
            "Sponsor a 5 month forum on American enterprise, spanning multiple topics": "C"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "How many years of service must one have to be eligible for the FBLA-PBL Adviser Hall of Fame?",
        "options": [
            "10",
            "15",
            "20",
            "25"
        ],
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: You can take a maximum of 3 objective tests in Regionals",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "FBLA stands for: Future ________ Leaders of America",
        "answer": "business"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are true about FBLA? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a college program",
            "It is a high school program",
            "It has an entry fee of $150"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a high school program"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "What is the full form of the BAA?",
        "answer": "business achievement awards"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the animals to their diets",
        "options": [
            "A) Carnivore",
            "B) Omnivore",
            "C) Herbivore"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Pig",
            "Lion",
            "Zebra",
            "Horse",
            "Hedgehog"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Pig": "B",
            "Lion": "A",
            "Zebra": "C",
            "Horse": "C",
            "Hedgehog": "B"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "When is American Enterprise Day?",
        "options": [
            "December 1",
            "November 15",
            "July 5",
            "August 23"
        ],
        "answer": "November 15"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: FBLA holds regional competitions",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "FBLA stands for: Future ________ Leaders of America",
        "answer": "business"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are true about FBLA? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a college program",
            "It is a high school program",
            "It has an entry fee of $150"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a high school program"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "What is the full form of the BAA?",
        "answer": "business achievement awards"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the animals to their diets",
        "options": [
            "A) Carnivore",
            "B) Omnivore",
            "C) Herbivore"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Pig",
            "Lion",
            "Zebra",
            "Horse",
            "Hedgehog"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Pig": "B",
            "Lion": "A",
            "Zebra": "C",
            "Horse": "C",
            "Hedgehog": "B"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "What does FBLA stand for?",
        "options": [
            "Future Blooming Leaders of America",
            "Future Business Leaders of America",
            "Future Bundle Leaders of America",
            "Future Business Leaders of Austria"
        ],
        "answer": "Future Business Leaders of America"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: FBLA holds regional competitions",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "FBLA stands for: Future ________ Leaders of America",
        "answer": "business"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are true about FBLA? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a college program",
            "It is a high school program",
            "It has an entry fee of $150"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a high school program"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "What is the full form of the BAA?",
        "answer": "business achievement awards"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the animals to their diets",
        "options": [
            "A) Carnivore",
            "B) Omnivore",
            "C) Herbivore"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Pig",
            "Lion",
            "Zebra",
            "Horse",
            "Hedgehog"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Pig": "B",
            "Lion": "A",
            "Zebra": "C",
            "Horse": "C",
            "Hedgehog": "B"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "What does FBLA stand for?",
        "options": [
            "Future Blooming Leaders of America",
            "Future Business Leaders of America",
            "Future Bundle Leaders of America",
            "Future Business Leaders of Austria"
        ],
        "answer": "Future Business Leaders of America"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: FBLA holds regional competitions",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    }
]